（鈴井(すずい)）これ用意したんだ
This is for you. There's one million yen
inside. You saved me before, right?
100万円ある
前に僕を助けてくれたよね
その恩返しってわけじゃないけど
使ってほしいんだ
This isn't enough to repay you,
but please take it.
Knowing you, if you have money,
you can make more gambling.
夢子(ゆめこ)なら元手さえあれば
ギャンブルで稼げる
（夢子）ありがとうございます
Thank you.
あれだけの大敗のあとでも
Even after that awful defeat,
you'll believe in me and bet on me, right?
鈴井さんは私を信じて
ベットしてくださるんですね
しかし このお金は結構です
- But I don't need this money.
- Why?
えっ な… なんで？
（夢子）
実は生徒会から
全く返済の催促がないんです
The student council
hasn't actually asked me to pay any of it.
So, I still have the money.
だから まだ
お金は手元に残っているんですよ
そんな… うそだろ？
No, that's impossible. I've heard stories
about how brutal the student council is
生徒会の
容赦ない取り立ての話なんて
いくらでも聞くのに
about getting their money.
さあ どうしてでしょうか…
I couldn't say why.
あっ でも
代わりなのか分かりませんが
But they did send me this instead.
こんな物が届きました
（鈴井）人生計画表？
"Life plan"?
〜
（清華(さやか)）黄泉月(よもつき)さん
Yomotsuki.
黄泉月さん
（るな）ん？
２年華(はな)組の早乙女(さおとめ)芽亜里(めあり)さんが
面会を願っておりますが
Mary Saotome of Year Two, Flower Class,
has requested a meeting with us.
（るな）
う〜ん 会長いないけど
まあ 私でいいっしょ 通して
The president isn't here,
but I guess I can handle it. Send her in.
（清華）早乙女さん どうぞ
Come in, Saotome.
何か用？
You need something?
I'm busy, so keep it short.
私 忙しいから
手短にね〜
I received this booklet this morning
from the student council.
（芽亜里）
今朝方 生徒会から
こんなものが届いたのですが…
（るな）はあ？
このふざけた文章に
何の意味があるんですか？
What's the point
of this ridiculous document?
（るな）うん？
書いてあるとおりの
意味だよ〜ん
It means what it says.
（芽亜里）ふざけないでください！
Shut up! What is this disgusting text?
何なんですか！
この気持ち悪い文章は！
SENATOR SAYAMA...
ENGAGED TO ORITA...
（るな）だから
I just told you.
It's exactly what it says.
書いてあるとおりって
言ってんじゃん
そこに書いてあることは
Everything that it says
is just what's gonna happen.
そうなることに
なってんの！
はあ？
Yes! Level clear!
（チャラ〜ン）
（るな）よっしゃ クリア！
ほいっと
ふむふむ
ふえ〜 ラッキーじゃん
議員夫人だってさ〜
You're lucky!
You get to marry a Diet member!
まあ 折田(おりた)って
Well, Orita's a filthy lolicon.
きったないロリコンの
オッサンだから
私なら絶対 ごめんだけど〜
I'd never want to marry him.
でも優秀な地盤と
コネ持ってるから
But he's got plenty of money
and connections,
何事もなきゃ成功するよ！
so you'll succeed if nothing happens.
ってか することになってるしね
Actually, it's already been decided
that nothing will.
はあ？ することになってる？
Already been decided?
Yes, the decision's already been made.
ニャハッ 決定事項ってこと！
（芽亜里）
確かに この学園は 政財界に
It's true that this school
has heavy connections
強いつながりを
持っているのは事実
in the financial and political worlds.
でも…
But...
でも それが本当だとして
私が結婚？
Even if that's true, me, getting married?
するわけないでしょう？
知りもしない…
No way! I don't even know...
MITTENS
（るな）
君の意思なんて関係ないよ〜
It doesn't matter what you think.
The decision's been made.
もう決まってんだから
And there's lots of ways to force somebody
to do what you want.
人を強制的に従わせる方法なんて
いろいろあるしね
くっ… ふざけるな！
Shut up!
誰が従うか！ こんなもの！
I refuse to obey this.
（るな）じゃあ 金返せよ
Then pay us what you owe us.
If you can't,
that's what'll happen to you.
ニャハ 金返せなきゃ
マジでそうなるからね！
せいぜい 男を喜ばすテクでも
磨いときなよ〜
Better get good at pleasing a man.
ニャハハハ アハハハ…
（鈴井）
結婚とか出産とか
何の冗談だよ これ…
Marriage? Birth?
What kind of joke is this?
フフッ 飽きさせないですよね
この学園は…
This school never bores you, does it?
（鈴井）あっ
（夢子）
一生を管理下に置かれ
“配合相手”まで用意されている
Your life is placed under their control.
You're even given someone to breed with.
“家畜”が取り立てられるのは
A house pet pays with their whole life,
you see.
“人生そのもの”
というわけですね
THE GIRL WHO BECAME A HOUSE PET
（鈴井）
夢子 ひと事じゃないんだぞ
This is a big problem. If the student
council says they'll do it, they will.
生徒会はやると言ったら
きっとやる
そうですね
That's right.
If I can't pay back 300 million yen,
I'll truly become a house pet.
３億円返済できなければ
本当の意味で家畜になってしまう
不安 焦燥 怒りと絶望…
Uncertainty, apprehension, rage, despair.
見慣れた構内の景色でさえ
ゆがんで見えてきます
Even the very halls of the school
seem twisted and different.
この感覚…
This feeling...
たまらない
it's wonderful.
（鈴井）あ…
（木渡(きわたり)）おい 蛇喰(じゃばみ)夢子
Hey, Yumeko Jabami.
お前 ミケになったんだってな
I heard you're Mittens now.
ちょっと つきあえよ
Come with me.
Kiwatari, from the Camellia Class.
椿(つばき)組の木渡
Yes, that's fine.
ええ かまいませんよ
行きましょうか
Let's go.
随分 遠くまで来ましたね
We've come a long way.
それで 私に
どのような用でしょうか？
So, what do you want from me?
服を脱げ ストリップしろ
Take your clothes off. Strip.
Damn it! What are they talking about?
（鈴井）
クソッ 何 話してんだ？
はあ！
（木渡）フフフ
（子分たち）うっ お〜
フフフッ
（子分たち）ふ〜 うわ〜
あっ！
（夢子）ああ もしかして…
（木渡）ん？
Oh, perhaps...
私に乱暴しようと
なさっているのですか？
Did you intend to get violent with me?
はあ？ そこまで言ってねえだろ
さっさと脱げよ
I didn't say that. Now, get naked.
う〜ん やっぱり お断りします
I refuse.
I don't want to let someone I don't know
see me naked, and you people are...
見知らぬ人に
肌を見せるのは嫌ですし
それに あなた方は…
私のタイプから 大外れしてるので
very far from my type.
（子分Ｂ）うわ！
てめえ 上等だよ
If that's how you want it.
If you want to get raped, fine.
望みどおり犯してやる
夢子！
Yumeko!
- Hey, there.
- Stay out of this.
（子分Ａ）おっと
（子分Ｂ）邪魔すんじゃねえぜ
（子分Ａ）
へへッ おとなしく見てなって
Just stand there and watch.
（鈴井）くっ…
（妄(みだり)）お〜い
Hey, what are you doing?
あんたら何やってんの？
（子分Ａ）ぎっ
（子分Ｂ）うわ…
んだ てめえ
- Who the hell are you?
- Hey, this is bad!
おっ おい ヤバいよ
生徒会役員
美化委員長の生志摩(いきしま)妄だよ！
That's Midari Ikishima,
the student council
beautification officer!
（子分Ａ）うわ！
（妄）ハハッ
無理やりは よくないな
It's not nice to get violent.
As the beautification officer,
I'll have to stop you.
美化委員長として
止めざるをえないじゃ〜ん
そんなにたまってんなら
あたしがしてやんよ
Listen, if you need it that bad...
I'll do it with you.
はあ？
（妄）
ただし タダってわけには
いかねえよ
But it'll cost you.
（子分Ａ）ぶはっ
もちろん
Of course!
ギャンブルで決めようぜ！
We gamble for it.
（鈴井）あ！
（木渡）ぐっ…
（妄）
こん中には１発だけ弾が入ってる
One of these chambers has a bullet in it.
今から１回 引き金を引くから
I'll pull the trigger once. If no bullet
comes out, I'll do whatever you want.
弾が出なきゃ 何でもしてやる
弾が出たら あんたは
And if the bullet comes out,
it blows you inside out.
あべこべに
突っ込まれるってわけよ
どう 面白れえっしょ？
- Well? Fun, huh?
- You're not making a damn bit of sense.
訳 分かんねえこと
言ってんじゃねえよ
分っかんねえな〜
I don't get it!
そんなに撃たれるのが怖(こえ)えわけ？
Are you that scared? There's
a five out of six chance to screw me.
６分の５でヤレんだぜ？
If I was in your place,
I'd take you up on it immediately.
あたしが逆の立場だったら
速攻 受けるけどな〜
逆…
In your place...
That's it! We switch places!
そうだ！ 逆だ！
You shoot!
あんたが撃ちなよ！
If the gun doesn't fire, just go home.
弾が出なかったら おとなしく帰れ
And if it does...
弾が出たら… ウヘッ
あたしは とても抵抗できる状態
じゃないだろうから
I won't be in a position to resist,
so you can do whatever you want.
何だってできるぞ！
あんたに不利益は一切なし！
You've got nothing to lose.
And everything to gain, right?
最高の条件だろう？
誰が どう考えたって
“撃つ”一択！
The only choice here is to shoot!
さあ撃て！ ほら 撃て！
Now, shoot! Come on! Shoot!
何 言ってんだ お前
What are you talking about?
バッカじゃねえの？
Are you stupid?
Man, that killed the mood. Let's go.
あ〜 萎えた 帰ろうぜ
（子分Ａ）
あっ ああ 俺も萎えちまったぜ
- It killed the mood for me too.
- Really!
（子分Ｂ）ホント ホント
（妄）あ？
Why are you leaving? Show some guts!
Don't you want to do it with me?
なんで帰ってんだよ！
根性見せろ！
やる気ねえのか お前ら！
（鈴井）夢子！ 大丈夫？
Yumeko, are you okay?
Suzui? Yes, I'm fine.
鈴井さん ええ 私は平気です
ハア〜
Ikishima.
（鈴子）生志摩さん
（妄）あ？
助けていただいて
ありがとうございました
Thank you for saving me.
（妄）はあ〜
- Yeah...
- I won't forget this debt.
このご恩は忘れません！
きっと何かの形で
お返しをさせていただきます
I'm sure I'll repay you somehow.
（木渡）
っとに あの女
頭おかしいんじゃねえか？
Is that bitch crazy?
（子分Ａ）
生徒会って
見るからに変人集団だしな
The student council's a bunch of weirdos.
（子分Ｂ）
ホント マンガじゃねえんだから
They're like right out of some comic book.
（木渡）でもよ〜
Seriously!
今回もヤツらのおかげで
ひともうけ できるぜ
But thanks to those guys,
we can make some money.
感謝しねえとなあ
We have to be grateful.
Damn it!
（妄）クソが！
ああ 物足りねえ
It's not enough.
じらすだけ
じらしやがって
They just got me all hot and bothered!
Those bastards!
あの野郎ども！
Damn it!
ああ クソ！ クソ！
クソ！ クソ！
ハア ハア
ハア〜
ハア…
Just once.
１回
I'll just do it once...
１回やっちまおう
６分の１
One in six.
６分の１で…
ハア〜
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
（カチッ）
ハハッ ヒャ ヒャ アハハハ…
これ これだよ！
This! This is it!
今 ここで あたしは生きてる！
I'm alive right now!
この感じ！
This feeling...
はあ ああ スゲ〜
Wow, it's amazing!
うっ… はあ〜
蛇喰夢子 だったか
Yumeko Jabami, was it?
ウヘッ
たっぷり お礼してもらおう
You're going to pay me back big-time.
（鈴井）
さっきは危なかった
That was a close one.
女子は家畜になったとき
男より もっと悲惨かもしれない
It's worse for a girl
to become a house pet than a boy.
早急に何とかしないと…
I need to do something fast.
夢子 これから
どこかの賭場にでも…
Yumeko, want to go to a gambling hall?
ん… 何 読んでるの？
What are you reading?
A flyer they were handing out in the hall.
（夢子）
先ほど
廊下で配られていたチラシです
（鈴井）
債務整理大集会のお知らせ？
"Notice of Debt Settlement Party"?
DEBT SETTLEMENT PARTY
（るな）
せいぜい 男を喜ばすテクでも
磨いときなよ〜
Better learn how to please a man!
ニャハハハ…
くっ
What kind of gambling
will we do today?
（男子生徒Ａ）
今日は 何のギャンブル
やんだろな？
If you win, great,
but if you lose, it's hell.
（男子生徒Ｂ）
勝てばいいけど 負けたら地獄だぜ
（女子生徒）
ねえ 私やっぱ やめようかな
Maybe I'll drop out.
（清華）
皆様 ようこそ 債務整理大集会へ
Welcome to the Debt Settlement Party.
生徒会書記 五十嵐(いがらし)清華です
I am Sayaka Igarashi,
secretary of the student council.
我が学園では
Every year, our school has students
who have trouble with their debts.
借金のため 首が回らなくなる方が
毎年発生します
So, the student council has provided them
with an opportunity.
そこで生徒会は
救済企画をご用意いたしました
その名も“借金 付け替えゲーム”
We call it the Debt Swap Game.
４人１組で
ギャンブルをしていただき
You will gamble in groups of four
and swap debts based on your performance.
成績に応じて
借金が そっくり入れ替わります
１位になれば 借金は
グループで最も少ない人の額に
Rank first and you'll swap with the person
with the lowest debt in the group.
４位なら最も高い額に
Rank fourth and you'll get the worst.
Your debt is swapped.
借金が付け替わるというわけです
いちばん借金が少ない人には
メリットがない？
The person with the least debt has
nothing to gain, you say? That's not true.
そんなことはありません
その場合は借金を免除します
In that case, your debt is erased.
さあ皆様 再チャレンジです
Now, everyone,
it's time for a second chance.
Take good advantage of this chance.
このチャンスを
ぜひ つかんでください
チッ 偽善者が
Hypocrites...
（夢子）
随分と気前のいいことですね
That's awfully nice of them.
Is there something in it
for the student council?
生徒会は
何かメリットがあるのでしょうか？
うわ 蛇喰夢子！
- Yumeko Jabami!
- Hello.
こんにちは
MITTENS
あ… フッ フン
あんた あのあと
生徒会に大負けしたんだってね
I heard you lost bad
to the student council.
はい ついうっかり
Yes, I slipped up.
早乙女さんも
集会に参加なさってたんですね
You're participating
in the party too, huh?
大きなお世話よ
It's none of your business.
Whose fault do you think this is?
誰のせいで
こうなったと思ってんの？
そう言わずに〜
Don't be like that.
We're classmates, right?
同じクラスの
よしみではありませんか
（芽亜里）
ウッゼ〜
（清華）
それでは 用紙を配りますので
I will now hand out applications.
ここに ご自分の借金先と
その額を申告してください
Write down the name of your creditor
and the amount owed.
皆様の多くは多重債務者
Many of you owe debts in smaller amounts
to multiple creditors.
つまり多数の相手に
細かく借金を抱えている
That would be enough to ruin anyone.
これでは誰しも
追い詰められてしまいます
このゲームを通して
生徒会へ借金を一本化し
Use this game as an opportunity
to transfer all your debts
再チャレンジを目指しましょう
to the student council!
（芽亜里）
要は搾取した金を
They're basically taking the money
they've stolen
借金まみれの生徒に返して
感謝させてるだけ
and giving it back to students
to make them grateful.
面の皮が厚いにも ほどがある
How shameless.
But their real goal is probably...
おそらく生徒会は…
（清華）
それでは組み合わせを発表します
I will now announce the pairings.
Team A, Year One, Flower Class,
Karen Mozu.
Ａ班 １年華組 百舌(もず)カレン
１年椿組…
Year One, Camellia Class, Jun Kiwatari.
（芽亜里）
こいつ 借金３億１千万
あるらしいからな
She's 310 million yen in debt.
I don't want to be on her team.
絶対 同じ班にはなりたくない
Year Two, Flower Class, Yumeko Jabami.
（清華）２年華組 蛇喰夢子
２年華組 早乙女芽亜里
Year Two, Flower Class, Mary Saotome.
早乙女さん
よろしくお願いしますね
I'm so glad to be on your team, Saotome!
（芽亜里）
ああ クソッ
私はこいつに呪われてんのか！
Damn it! Did she put a curse on me?
さて では ギャンブルの内容に
移りましょう
Let's move on to the game itself.
You will be playing two-card Indian poker.
今回 皆様に用意したギャンブルは
２枚インディアンポーカー
ルールは簡単
The rules are simple.
You'll use a 40-card deck
with jokers and face cards removed.
ジョーカーと絵札を除いた
40枚のトランプを使います
まずディーラーが皆様に
The dealer will first hand out one card
to each of you, so take a look.
１枚目のカードを配りますので
確認してください
次に２枚目のカードが配られます
The second card will then be passed out.
Don't look at this.
Just put it up on your head.
こちらは自分では見ずに
頭の上に掲げます
公開カードと非公開カード
You have a visible card and a hidden card.
These two will be your tools.
この２枚の組み合わせで勝負します
２枚の数字が一致する
“ペア”が最強
The strongest hand is a "pair,"
where both numbers match.
２枚のマークが同じ
“マーク”が次点
Next, a "suit," where both cards
have the same suit.
数字もマークもそろわない
“ブタ”が最弱
The weakest is a "pig,"
where neither the suit nor number matches.
同じ役なら
If all players have the same hand,
the largest number wins.
数字の合計数が
大きいほうが勝ちです
そして ここからが
このゲームの面白いところです
And this is where the game
gets interesting.
You'll be given ten chips
of varying colors.
皆様には色の異なるチップを
10枚お配りします
The number of chips
isn't that important in this game
このゲーム
チップの枚数は
さほど重要ではありません
because it will be the sum value
of your chips that determines the winner.
というのも 最終的に
チップの合計金額で
勝負を決するからです
チップの価値は
その人の申告額を10で割った額
A chip's value is the owner's debt
divided by ten.
借金が１億円なら
１枚１千万円になります
If the total debt is 100 million,
one chip is 10 million.
ゲームは10ターン行い
The game will take place over ten turns.
Players will pay one chip to participate.
ターンごとに参加費として
自分のチップが１枚必要です
また一度に賭けられるチップは
５枚までとします
And you can only bet
up to five chips at once.
（芽亜里）
私のチップは１枚500万
My chips are worth
five million yen apiece.
対して夢子は3100万円
And Yumeko's are worth 31 million?
この違いが どう影響するか
How will this affect the game?
（清華）最後になりますが
Lastly, we will provide no help.
我々は一切の助言をいたしません
それはイカサマも同じ
This includes cheating.
勝負の世界では
だまされるほうが悪いのです
In the world of gambling,
the person who's deceived is at fault.
指摘されれば 止めますが
If it's pointed out, we'll stop them, but
even then, we won't nullify past winnings.
その場合でも過去の行為まで
遡及(そきゅう)して無効にはなりません
説明は以上です
That's the only explanation we'll give.
Good luck, everyone.
皆様のご健闘を お祈りいたします
（夢子）
さっ 私たちも参りましょうか？
Okay, let's go!
（芽亜里）
クソッ これだけは
やりたくなかったが…
Damn it! This is the one thing
I didn't want to do, but...
蛇喰さん
ちょっと話があるんだけど
Jabami, I need to talk to you...
（夢子）ん？
TEAM F DEBT SETTLEMENT PARTY
（清華）お待ちしておりました
- We've been waiting for you.
- You're the dealer?
あなたがディーラーを？
Yes, this group has by far
the largest debts.
ええ この卓は
ぶっちぎり１番の高額卓
We can't allow any problems to occur.
何か間違いがあっては
いけませんからね
よう 夢子
縁があるなあ お前とは
Hey, Yumeko.
Guess fate brought us together again.
ウフフ 奇遇ですね
- What a coincidence, huh?
-Kiwatari...
（芽亜里）木渡君
（木渡）はあ？
あなた 家畜票は？
Where's your tag?
（木渡）聞いてなかったのか？
Didn't you listen?
You write down your own amount of debt.
借金は自己申告って言ってたろ？
I'm not a house pet,
but I'm saying I owe a friend money.
俺は家畜でも何でもねえが
ダチに借金したことにしてあんだよ
そうすりゃ
生徒会から肩代わりとして
This means the student council
will pay my friend ten million yen.
ダチに１千万 支払われる
ここで勝って返済免除にすれば
丸もうけってわけだ
If I win, I don't have to pay it back.
It's free money.
You're very confident.
You know you might go into debt over this.
随分 自信がおありなんですね
借金を負う可能性もあるのに
ハッ この集会で
俺は今までに３回勝った
I've won this game three times.
てめえら家畜なんぞに
負けるわけねえ
I won't lose to you house pets.
落ちてる金を拾うようなもんだ
It's like picking money off the ground.
He's saying that
right to the student council's face?
（芽亜里）
こいつ 生徒会の前で堂々と
スルーか
She's ignoring him, huh?
This might force the student council
to take unnecessary losses,
生徒会にとっては
無駄な損を出しかねない話だが
あくまで自己申告ってことか
but they're letting anybody
write down what they want.
We will now begin two-card Indian poker.
それでは これより
２枚インディアンポーカー
始めさせていただきます
まずは 参加費をお支払いください
First, pay your fee.
Look at your card and place it face down.
このカードは確認したら
場に伏せてください
これは ご自分では見ずに
頭の上に掲げてください
Don't look at the next card.
Simply put it on your head.
それでは 親の木渡様からどうぞ
We'll start with Kiwatari, the dealer.
（木渡）さて どうすっか…
Now, what to do...
It'd be boring to fold on the first round.
I'm betting one Kiwatari chip.
最初から降りても つまらねえ
ベット 木渡１枚だ
（奈々美(ななみ)）コール 蕾(つぼみ)１枚
Call. One Tsubomi chip.
（芽亜里）
当然だな
Of course. The lower the value
of the chips, the lower the risk.
チップの額が低ければ
リスクも少ない
ガツガツ勝負するのが正解だが
私たちは そうはいかない
The right answer is to bet big,
but we're not doing that.
ここは慎重に
- Let's be careful, and...
- Call. One Jabami chip.
（夢子）コール 蛇喰１枚
はあ？ 何やってんの あんた！
What are you doing?
Do you know the cost of those chips?
自分のチップ額 分かってる？
始めから降りていては
勝負になりませんよ
You can't play a game if you won't play at
the start. I have to play at some point.
どうせ いつかは
勝負しなければいけないですし
But that doesn't mean...
いや だからって…
ハッ いいねえ 強気！
Bold! I like it!
Is she crazy?
（芽亜里）
大丈夫か こいつ…
フォールド
Fold.
Calls are complete. Show your hands.
宣言終了です
手札を開示してください
Seven and eight. A pig.
７ ８のブタですね
３ ６のブタです
Three, six, pig.
３ ９のマーク 俺の勝ちだな
Three, nine, suit. I win.
Kiwatari wins, so all chips are his.
木渡様の勝利ですので
供託されたチップは
全て木渡様の物です
（芽亜里）
言わんこっちゃない
I told you...
（清華）２ターン目に参ります
Moving to turn two.
親は 蕾様に交代です
Tsubomi is now the dealer.
Bet. One Tsubomi chip.
ベット 蕾１枚
フォールドです
Fold.
フォールド
Raise. Four Kiwatari chips.
（木渡）レイズだ 木渡４枚
フォールド
Fold.
（木渡）はあ？
木渡様以外の全員が
フォールドですので
Everyone but Kiwatari has folded,
so he wins.
木渡様の勝利です
You guys are a bit too wimpy, huh?
お前ら弱気がすぎねえか〜
そんなことだから
家畜になっちまうんだよ
That's how you end up as house pets.
相手になんねえ雑魚が！
You aren't even worth my time.
（清華）
では ３ターン目に参ります
Moving to turn three.
（夢子）
う〜ん なかなか いいカードが
来ましたね
This is a good card.
ここはベットで 蛇喰１枚
I'll bet one Jabami chip.
ヘッ やっと勝負にきたか
You're finally ready to play, huh?
レイズだ 木渡２枚
Raise. Two Kiwatari chips.
Oh, my. Two chips?
あら ２枚？
お言葉を返すようですが
少し弱気ではありませんか？
To repeat what you said earlier,
isn't that a bit too wimpy?
（木渡）いいんだよ これは戦略だ
It's okay. This is a strategy.
ほかとは桁が違う
If I end up giving up your chips,
お前のチップを吐き出す
なんてことになったら
which are so much more valuable
than the others, that'd be a disaster!
目も当てられねえ
Yumeko, getting your chips
is my top priority.
夢子 お前のチップは
“確保”一択なんだよ
And I'm not letting go of them.
ぜってえ放出しねえ
そうですか
I see. Then I'll go ahead and win this.
なら 遠慮なく
勝たせていただきますね
レイズ 蛇喰３枚
Raise. Three Jabami chips.
What?
なにっ!?　ぎっ…
YUMEKO CHIPS
面白れえ
All right, then.
コールだ 木渡２枚
Call. Two Kiwatari chips.
宣言終了です
Calls are complete. Show your hands.
手札の開示を
ハッ 強運だね 俺も
Lady luck's with me, huh?
（芽亜里）
２ ５のマーク
A two, five, suit.
What a coincidence.
I'm confident in my luck too.
奇遇ですね
私も運には自信があるんですよ
４ 10のマークです
A four, ten, suit.
ぐっ…
（木渡）
こいつ…
She's...
（清華）
では ４ターン目 参ります
Moving to turn four.
The dealer is Saotome.
親は早乙女様です
（芽亜里）
ん…
Yumeko's right.
At some point, you have to play the game.
夢子の言うとおり
いつかは勝負に
いかなければならない
ならば…
So...
ベット 早乙女１枚
Bet. One Saotome chip.
コール 木渡１枚
Call. One Kiwatari chip.
Fold.
フォールド
コール 木渡１枚
Call. One Kiwatari chip.
（芽亜里）
ここで負ければ 私の人生は
If I lose here, my life will follow
that ridiculous plan.
あのふざけた人生計画表
どおりになる
I'll marry a politician, have his child,
and become the wife of a Diet member.
政治家と結婚し 子供をもうけ
議員夫人となる
My husband will become education minister,
夫は文部科学大臣にまで出世し
and my three children
will all succeed in life.
３人の子供は それぞれ立派に独立
愛する夫と共に
I'll spend my last years
子供や孫に囲まれた温かな老後を
大過なく過ごし
surrounded by a loving husband,
children, and grandchildren.
天寿を全うする
早乙女芽亜里は
女としての幸福を極めた
Mary Saotome will live the happiest life
a woman could ask for.
これ以上 望みようのない人生を
送ることになる
そんなものクソくらえだ！
Screw that!
私の人生は私のもの！
My life is mine!
誰にも渡さない
I won't let anyone have it!
I'll take my life back!
私は 私の人生を取り戻す！
Raise. Three Saotome Chips!
レイズ 早乙女３枚！
SAOTOME CHIPS
（清華）
ほう…
（木渡）フッ バカか おめえ
Are you stupid?
夢子のあとなら こっちがビビッて
フォールドすると思ったか？
You think after Yumeko won,
I'd fold and get scared?
ここで俺が勝てば お前は残り２枚
If I win, you'll only have two chips.
You won't be able to come back from that.
逆転は不可能だ コール
Call.
（木渡）するわけねえだろ
（芽亜里）あ！
Of course, I'm not that dumb.
（木渡）
見え透いてんだよ 家畜ども
I know what you're up to, house pets.
Saotome, Yumeko, you're working together.
早乙女 夢子 てめえらグルだろ？
（芽亜里）うっ！
（木渡）あからさますぎんだよ
It's way too obvious. In this game,
you can only see one of your cards.
このゲームは
自分の手を１枚しか見れない
どんなに
数字の大きいカードが来ても
No matter the number,
you'll lose to a suit,
約４分の１の確率でそろう
マークに負ける
which has a one in four chance
of occurring.
（夢子）
う〜ん なかなか いいカードが
来ましたね
This is a good card.
（木渡）
そんなセリフは
ありえねえんだよ！
What you said is impossible.
その不確定な手に
And it's even more impossible
that you'd bet 155 million
１億5500万も賭けるなんてことは
もっとありえねえ！
on something so uncertain.
とすれば 簡単な話
It's simple. You were able to do that
because you knew you had a suit.
自分がマークだってことを
知ってるから できたわけだ
通しがあるのは明らか
It's obvious you're cheating.
残念だったな〜
Too bad. House pets can't fool humans.
家畜のやることなんざ
人間様には お見通しなんだよ
フォールドだ
Fold.
ああ…
（清華）蛇喰様？
Jabami?
フォールドです
Fold.
（木渡）
テッヘヘヘ よし！
Yes! I was able to cut my losses to two!
ヤツの役を２枚の損害で防いだ
この調子なら余裕で勝てる！
At this rate, I can win easy.
（芽亜里）目ざといね あなた
（木渡）はあ？
You're sharp. I guess
when you're doing bad things every day,
毎日 悪いことばかりしてると
悪意に敏感になるのかな
you know when someone's out to get you.
何にせよ 勝負に出てよかった
Anyway, I'm glad I went big.
This gives me a bullet to use.
これで弾が出来た
（木渡）何を言って…
What are you...?
ががっ！
フフッ
アハッ 私の手はブタだよ！
My hand was a pig, fool!
バ〜カ！
〜
（木渡）
何だと！
- What?
- It's more fun when you cheat!
（夢子）
イカサマありのほうが
面白いと思うんです
- He who lies best wins.
- I had a pig and still won!
（芽亜里）
ブタなのに勝っちゃった！
（夢子）
もはや この勝負
This game is...
nothing but a series of bluffs!
ブラフ合戦と成り果てました！
EPISODE 5
THE GIRL WHO BECAME HUMAN